本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译
最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译    Z小花儿    Dzysteven      补课狂魔
翻译    小胖纸Amy     Silence
翻译   Charl   Murrayzhang
翻译   DustD  明日绽放
校对 Z小花儿  DustD  精校  传奇小闪迷
时间轴  Youliss   想念Gallifrey的wholock
特效& 后期   咖啡・Lee  总监  苹果果
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
2166年  永生的暴君汪达尔・萨维奇
In 2166, an immortal tyrant named Vandal Savage
征服了世界  杀害了我的妻儿
conquered the world and murdered my wife and child.
我招募了一个精英团队  穿越时间去寻找他
I have assembled an elite team to hunt him throughout time
并阻止他取得霸权
and stop his rise to power.
不幸的是  我的计划遭到
Unfortunately, my plan is opposed
我曾发誓效忠的组织
by the body I'd sworn my allegiance to:
时间之主的反对
the Time Masters.
未来  我的朋友们或许不是英雄
In the future, my friends may not be heroes,
但倘若此举成功
but if we succeed,
他们将会成为传奇  被世人铭记
they will be remembered as legends.
《明日传奇》前情提要
Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
我们停在时光穿梭区  我不明白
We're in the Temporal Zone. I don't understand.
应该没人能...
No one should be able to--
船体的扫描结果显示
A scan of the vessel suggests
是赏金猎手克罗诺斯在袭击我们
that it is the bounty hunter, Kronos.
无法决定
A crash landing--
迫降的地点和时间
in both place and time.
吉迪恩  把船伪装起来
Gideon, camouflage the ship.
这里不会是我们
This doesn't look like the type of place
想在外逗留很久的地方
we want to linger out in the open.
那栋挺像帕尔默科技大楼
That looks a lot like a Palmer Tech building,
但为什么是斯莫克的标志
but why does it have a Smoak logo on it?
等下  这里是星城
Wait, this is Star City.
你不是说时间线安全了吗
I thought you said the timeline was safe.
星城在2016年没有毁坏
Yes, Star City was intact in 2016.
但这是...这是2046年
This--this is 2046.
不许动
Don't move!
谢天谢地
Thank God.
我说了不许动
I said don't move.
是我
It's me.
我是莎拉
It's Sara.
奥利弗
Hey, Oliver, look.
我知道有段时间了
I know it's been a long time.
你是不是忘记
But don't you remember that Rip Hunter
我们被里普・亨特招募去当传奇了
recruited us to become legends?
我从来没听过任何传奇
I never heard of any Legends.
退后
Get back!
这是你朋友吗  我不喜欢他
This guy a friend of yours? I don't like him.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
这叫还击
It's called shooting back.
不可能是绿箭侠
Can't be the Green Arrow.
他不是奥利弗・奎恩
That's not Oliver Queen.
可穿得很像他
Sure dresses like him.
射箭也像他
Shoots arrows like him.
不管他是谁  我可不想留在这里
Well, whoever he is, I don't plan on sticking around
被这哥们儿串成肉串
to shish kebabbed by this dude.
小兄弟说得对
Kid's right.
那咱们就在这干掉他
Let's stay behind and kill him.
你去控制飞船
We need you in charge of the ship.
明日传奇
第一季第六集
星城  2046年
好了  里普  说实话吧
All right, Rip. Tell us the truth.
你们都看到时间线固定前
You've all seen how the timeline is malleable--
是如何延展变化的
in flux until it is set.
这个未来还没固定
Well, this future is not set.
还记得我说过你们对自己的未来
Remember when I told you it was dangerous
知道太多是非常危险的
for any of you to know too much about your own futures?
你害怕发生的事极有可能
Well, the events that you dread could very well come to be
因为你去阻止而成为现实
due to your actions to prevent them.
知道我怎么想吗  我认为你想太多了
You know what I think? I think you think too much.
我得说  为了你们自己和这项任务
Believe me when I tell you that the best thing
现在当务之急
for yourselves and for this mission
你们要在2046年把乘波号修好
is to make the repairs to the Waverider here in 2046
然后回到你们的年代
then head back to your own time
确保这些永远不会发生
and make sure that none of this ever comes to be.
看来整个推进系统都坏掉了
Looks like the whole propulsion system's jacked.
你怎么知道我们要在这里检查什么
How do you even know what we're looking at here?
只要肯费时间  其他就不重要了
Doesn't matter if it takes you down the road or through time.
引擎总归是引擎
An engine's still an engine.
要花多久才能修好
How long will it take you to make repairs?
不确定  要是有人帮忙
I'm not too sure, but it would go a lot faster
我会快一点
if I had some help.
肯德拉或许能帮我的忙
Maybe Kendra could lend me a hand?
谁有空就找谁帮忙吧
Enlist whoever is free to help,
我得处理这个
I have this to contend with.
这是吉迪恩逻辑和导航模型的
This is the Neuromorphic Interface
神经形态接口
for Gideon's logic and navigation matrix.
吉迪恩没了这个就无法工作
Without it, Gideon cannot function.
难怪我们会被困在未来
Well, that explains how we got stranded here in the future.
帕尔默科技当时在研究
Palmer Tech was working on
有自主学习功能的神经形态皮质
a self-learning, Neuromorphic Cortex.
到2046年他们肯定已经造出原型了
They surely would have gone to prototype by 2046.
我们需要那个原型
We are going to need that prototype.
帕尔默科技现在成了斯莫克科技
Ah, Palmer Tech is now Smoak Technologies,
不过我还是能带大家进去
but, uh, I'm sure I can still get us in.
我说过  你和兰斯小姐
As I said, we must keep you and Ms. Lance
不能接触你们未来的家园
separate from your future homes.
总之  我招募这些
In any case, there's a reason
擅长偷盗他人财产的人
why I recruited individuals
是有原因的
adept at misappropriating others' property.
不是钱财  不是珠宝
It's not money. It's not jewels.
也不是什么珍贵文物
It's not a valuable artifact.
你就庆幸我现在什么都肯偷吧
You're just lucky I'll steal anything right about now.
-如我所料  -我们会拿到你要的玩意
- As I suspected. - We'll get your gizmo.
你只管让这铁桶飞起来就行
You just get this bucket flying again.
-我也去  -不  你不能去
- I'm coming with. - No, no you are not.
你和这座城市有太多的羁绊
You're too emotionally connected to the city.
-我们谈过这个了 -我受够你了
- We've been over this. - I'm over you.
你让我们为了你
You got us on a mission
执行改变时间线的任务
to change the timeline for yourself.
却不让我们看看自己的未来
And you won't even let us look at our futures?
我比任何人都了解这座城市
Now, I know this city better than anyone else,
你们需要我的帮忙
and you're gonna need me out there.
所以  要么我也一起去
So, either I'm coming with,
要么就看看在教人打架方面
or we can find out if the Time Masters
是时间之主厉害
are as good at teaching people to fight
还是刺客联盟厉害
as the League of Assassins.
其他队友去以前的帕尔默科技
So the rest of the team's on a field trip to Palmer Tech,
现在的斯莫克科技出勤了
now Smoak Technologies.
帕尔默科技比较好听  对吧
Palmer Tech sounds better, right?
跟我说实话
Be honest.
实际上  听起来都一样
Honestly, they sound about the same.
就算我们的队友能拿回来
Even assuming our compatriots return
那个神经形态原型
with a Neuromorphic prototype,
我们也需要让吉迪恩适应新装备
we'll still need to prepare Gideon for the new device.
而且引擎也急需修理
And the engines could definitely use some loving.
实际上  我需要一个帮手
Actually, I could use an extra pair of hands.
雷蒙德  要不然你和桑德斯小姐
Well, Raymond, why don't you and Ms. Saunders
继续修理吉迪恩
continue repairing Gideon,
然后我去帮杰佛逊修引擎
and I'll assist Jefferson with the engines?
这个未来还没固定
This is just a potential future.
我们杀几个人没什么关系  对吧
It doesn't matter if we kill anyone here, right?
为了避免产生时间悖论的危险
Well, to avoid the risk of a paradox,
也许我们还是不杀人比较合适
it's probably best to refrain from killing anyone.
我可不能保证什么
I'm not gonna promise anything.
我姐姐的公寓之前在这边
My sister's apartment used to be over here.
我好像记得
I seem to remember something
你爸爸是警察队长吧
about your father being a police captain.
-什么意思  -没把工作做好啊
- Your point? - Did one hell of a job.
我爸爸和其他人
My father and everyone else
绝不会让这一切发生的
would never have let this happen...
除非他们都死了
unless they were all dead.
你还真挺擅长这个
You really are pretty good at this.
没错  我在1944年是个船坞焊工
Yeah, I was a shipyard welder in 1944.
不会吧  你是现实版铆钉女工萝西
No way. A real life Rosie the Riveter?
「二战时期  男性大多参战
美国工厂大量职位空缺
铆钉女工萝西
是激励百万女性投入工作
的著名海报形象」
任何事你都能
Is there anything you can't manage
往正面方向想吗
to put a positive spin on?
我想到了  车管局
No, I got it: the DMV.
所以你还真有黑暗的一面
So you do have a dark side.
你在取笑我吗
You making fun of me?
有点吧
Little bit.
我觉得你一直这么乐观
Doesn't mean I don't find your unwavering optimism...
挺可爱的
enjoyable.
我觉得看你焊接也挺可爱
I find watching you weld enjoyable.
帕尔默博士  提醒你一下
Dr. Palmer, in case you weren't aware,
你们现在正在公放
you are on an open channel,
你们说的话我们都能听见
and we can hear everything you're saying.
让大家专业点工作
Is it too much to ask
这个要求太过分了吗
for some professionalism around here, and--
我为什么这么生气
why am I getting so upset?
稍等片刻
One moment, please.
我并没有生气  是你生气了
I'm not upset. You're upset.
我没有
No, I'm not.
我的血压飙升  证明你有
My elevated blood pressure confirms that you are.
我只是
I'm just--
我只是很烦那两个人
I'm just getting annoyed that those two
光说话不干活
are talking instead of working.
我是说
I mean...
-你喜欢她  -老兄  你疯了
- You like her. - Dude, you're being crazy.
你记得我们俩是
You do remember that we share
心灵相通的吧
a psychic connection.
我能感觉到你的情感
I can sense what you're feeling.
要是这样  你就闭嘴吧
If that were true, then you would shut up.
我现在也不轻松
Hey, it's no day at the beach for me, either.
相信我
Believe me.
没关系
Well, it doesn't matter,
反正我和她不可能
'cause I don't stand a chance with her anyway.
为什么要那么说
Now, why would you say that?
因为此时此刻  我的情敌是
Because right now, my competition
给自己造了超级战衣的亿万富豪天才
is a billionaire genius who built his own super-suit
和一个她相识了四千年
and some other dude she's known for 4,000 years
命中注定会在一起的家伙
who she is destined to be with.
我想给你提一点建议
If I may offer one word of advice--
你还是别提了
I really wish you wouldn't.
我想你"自信点"
That word would be "Confidence."
你见过年轻时候的我
You met my younger self.
我当时可是很有女人缘的
I was quite the ladies' man.
好好表现自己
Put yourself out there.
会有好结果的
Good things will happen.
从这边走两个街区就是帕尔默科技了
Palmer Tech's just two blocks up this way.
或者说至少以前在那里
Or at least it used to be.
快去那边找掩护
Take cover in there!
外面简直像第三次世界大战
It's like World War III out there.
太美妙了
It's beautiful.
很快回来
We need to find another route.
兰斯小姐  别去  莎拉
Ms. Lance, don't. Sara!
该死的
Damn it!
你们俩呆着别动  我们去去就回
You two--don't move. We'll be right back.
好的
Right.
我们不会就待在这吧
We're not gonna sit here, right?
想想我们能趁乱劫走的宝贝
Imagine all the looting we can do in this chaos.
我们何不去往回走三个街区的银行
Why don't we stretch our legs at that bank we passed
活动下筋骨
three blocks back?
放下武器  把钱包交出来
Drop your weapons, and hand over your wallets.
等等  你真的准备抢劫我们吗
Wait, are you actually trying to mug us?
这算什么  外行当道吗
What is this, amateur hour?
你们如果不按我手下说的做
If you don't do what my man says,
我们只能把你们当蚂蚁一样踩扁了
we're gonna crush you into the pavement like a couple of ants.
搞笑吗
Really?
要不我们给这些人好好上一课吧
What do you say we teach these fellas a lesson?
好啊
Yeah.
这就是你不听话的下场
That's what you get when you don't follow directions.
有意思  帮我拿一下
Interesting. Hold this.
不如这样
Second thoughts...
你从哪弄来这玩意儿的
Where did you get that?
易趣
eBay.
你们老大现在用不着这个了
Now, your boss will not be needing this.
这确实很好玩
Well, this has been fun,
但我们该走了
but I think it's time to leave.
走
Leave?
我们为什么要走
Why would we leave?
来吧  甜心
Come on, sweetheart.
站住别动
Don't move.
你
You--
你还真是执着
you are persistent.
我看到你近距离挨了一枪
I saw you get shot point-blank.
这是高密度凯芙拉纤维  你到底是谁
It's high-density Kevlar, now...who the hell are you?
-你是谁  -我是绿箭侠
- Who are you? - I'm the Green Arrow.
奥利弗・奎恩才是绿箭侠
Oliver Queen is the Green Arrow.
不  他不是
No, he's not.
奥利弗・奎恩死了
Oliver Queen is dead.
奥利弗怎么死的
How did Oliver die?
我也不清楚  没人知道
I don't know. No one does.
自从大起义之后
No one's seen him since--
-就没人见过他了  -大起义
- well, since the Uprising. - Uprising?
大起义是人们给发生的
Is just what people called it when--
这一切所取的名字
well, when all this happened.
15年前  他率领着一支大军
15 years ago, he brought an army with him.
-谁率领着一支大军  -我
- Who brought an army? - I did.
不  这不可能
No, it's not possible.
你怎么从炼狱岛逃出来的
How did you get off Lian Yu?
该死的  说话阿
Say something, damn it!
兰斯小姐  这是谁
Ms. Lance? Who is this?
一个很危险的人
Somebody very dangerous.
虽然现在不该这么说
Then now is not the right time for me to say it--
但等下请提醒我告诉你我早说过了
but please, remind me later to tell you that I told you so.
斯莱德  你怎么还活着
How are you still alive, Slade?
斯莱德
Slade.
很久没听人说这个名字了
That's a name I haven't heard in a long time.
你怎么认识我父亲的
How do you know my father?
他叫你兰斯小姐
He called you Ms. Lance.
你和已故的兰斯队长什么关系
Any relation to the late Captain Lance?
如果有  你肯定听过我父亲的事
If so, you must have heard stories about my father.
我认识你父亲
I knew your father.
他是个疯子
He was insane.
而且好像还遗传给你了
Seems to run in the family.
我会享受杀你
I'm going to enjoy killing you--
或者我们都会
or we will.
这是个坏主意
Okay, bad idea.
来吧
Come on.
好啦
All right.
我和灰老头将干线重新连上了
Grey and I have got the mains back online.
太棒了
Great.
雷在修一个叫量子歧管的东西
Ray's working on something called the quantum manifold.
我好像修不好这玩意儿
But I can't seem to get this to cooperate.
让我来试试
Let me give it a try.
你好像很懂行啊
Hey, you actually seem to know what you're doing here.
是的  机械我最懂了
Uh, yeah, machines are kind of my thing.
而且我休息的时候一直在看
Plus, I've been looking at the instruction manual
操作手册  所以
in my downtime, so...
大多数人看操作手册
Most people can't follow
都无法拼出一个新书柜来
the instructions to build their new bookcase,
而你现在却在修一艘宇宙飞船
and here you are working on a spaceship.
而且还是一艘来自未来的时间飞船
A time-traveling spaceship from the future, no less.
被你这么一说
Well, when you put it like that,
我有点受宠若惊
I am kind of amazing.
不要骄傲
And humble.
如果你要组装书柜的话
Hey, if you ever have any bookcases need putting together--
我知道要找谁
I'll know who to call.
雷蒙德
So, Raymond,
你之前和肯德拉一起修理飞船时
you were working with Kendra earlier.
我注意到
I couldn't help but notice
你们俩之间似乎有一点...
there might've been a little...
火花
spark.
-真的吗  -是的
- Really? - Oh, yes.
挺明显的  而且如果我没搞错
It was quite apparent and if I'm not mistaken,
我发现她还朝你多看了几眼
I've noticed her throwing one or two glances your way.
这我可没想到
Wow, that's-- that's surprising.
-是吗  -当然
- Is it? - Well, yeah.
我不知道  我对她还真没那种想法
I don't know, I hadn't really considered her in that way.
你为什么要提这些
Why are you bringing this up?
天呐  感觉像回到了高中
Jeez, I feel like I'm back in high school.
说实话我不了解这些  我高一跳级了
I honestly wouldn't know. I skipped 10th grade.
还有高二
And 11th.
我和肯德拉没怎么单独相处过
I haven't really spent that much time with Kendra.
很多时候都是跟她的转世灵魂伴侣和
You know, other than time that we shared with her
想杀我们的人
and her reincarnated soulmate,
一起相处
or people trying to kill us.
所以我们更不该有私情
All the more reason to avoid personal attachments.
这艘船或许很大  但我们人不多
This ship may be large, but our group is small.
没错
Yeah.
我本来也是这么想的  教授
Preaching to the choir, Professor.
我们登上乘波号是为了拯救世界...
We're onboard the Waverider to save the world...
不是乱勾搭
not hook up.
是的  没错
Yes, quite right.
你们听着  我记不住名字
Hey, you, I'm terrible with names.
-我就叫你方兹  -好
- I'm gonna call you Fonzie. - Yeah!
-叫你柯尼基  -好
- I'm gonna call you Kenickie. - Yeah!
还有谁要我赐名字
Anyone else here need a name?
殿下  我能占用您一点时间吗
Your highness, can I get a moment of your time, please?
当然
Sure.
未来很棒吧
Isn't the future great?
我们真该回去找里普和莎拉了
We really should be getting back to Rip and Sara.
为什么
Why?
因为我可不想在这里扎根驻营
Cause I'm not looking to put down roots here.
为什么不呢  这是我们追求的一切
Why not? It's everything we've ever wanted.
我有一个帮派  对我言听计从
I got a gang that does everything I tell them to.
有裘皮大衣穿
I got a fur coat.
还有美酒喝
I got a chalice.
说到这个
Speaking of.
-不管萨维奇了吗  -怎么了
- What about stopping Savage? - What about it?
你说过我们加入
You're the one who said we're in
只是为了干一票  记得吗
this for the score, remember?
我们在这里可以像国王一样生活
We could live like kings here.
没有警察  没有英雄
No cops, no heroes--
只有穿着绿色连帽衫的傻瓜
just some fool in a green hoodie.
这里每天都是圣诞节
It's Christmas every day.
我的甜心
My sweet.
斯莱德有儿子吗
Slade had a son?
奥利弗尽力了
Look, Oliver tried.
他想招兵对抗丧钟  但是...
He tried to raise an army to fight Deathstroke, but...
大家只想离开这里
everyone just wanted to evacuate.
要怎么去拯救一座自暴自弃的城市呢
How can you save a city that doesn't want to be saved?
稍等片刻
A moment.
莎拉  我知道你在想什么
Sara, I know what you must be thinking,
但这里发生的一切都不是你的过错
but none of what has transpired here is your fault,
你也没有办法改变这一切
nor do you have the means to change it,
但可以阻止汪达尔・萨维奇未来的恶行
but Vandal Savage's future is preventable.
求你了
I implore you,
求你专注于我们的任务
please stay focused on our mission.
非常谢谢你帮我们
We're very grateful for your assistance,
但我们得出发去斯莫克科技了
but we really must be moving along to Smoak Technologies.
去干什么
What for?
那地方已经关闭好几年了
That place has been cleared out for years,
但费利西蒂・斯莫克的许多项目都转走了
but a lot of Felicity Smoak's projects got relocated.
在哪里
Where?
走吧
Come on.
你先前没说费利西蒂的设备会在这里
You didn't say that Felicity's equipment would be here.
不然你们觉得会在哪里呢
Well, where else would you think it'd be?
奎恩先生的行动基地
Mr. Queen's base of operations
已经今非昔比了
appears to have seen better days.
是的
Yeah, well...
格兰特・威尔逊揭露奎恩是绿箭侠后
the place got attacked after Grant Wilson
这地方就受到了攻击
outed Queen as the Green Arrow.
找到我们要的东西后就离开这里吧
Let's just find what we're looking for and get out of here.
谁在那里  出去
Whoever's there, get out.
我说了  出去
I said get out!
不管你是谁  出去
Whoever you are, get out.
奥利弗
Oliver?
你好  莎拉
Hello, Sara.
好久不见
Long time no see.
-那是不是  -奥利弗・奎恩
- Is that-- - Oliver Queen.
大家都以为你死了
Everyone thinks that you're dead.
没错
They're not wrong.
把箭放下  约翰
Put the arrow down, John.
你是在自找麻烦
You're embarrassing yourself.
-约翰  -是小约翰・狄格尔
- John? - John Diggle Junior.
我爸爸过世了
My dad is dead
因为我救不了他
because I couldn't save him.
我不配用他的名字  我叫康纳・霍克
I don't deserve his name. I'm Connor Hawke.
那你不用他的名字
So you won't take his name,
就能穿着别人的战衣到处巡游吗
but it's all right to parade around in someone else's outfit?
总得有人穿
Well, someone has to,
因为我以为你死了
because last time that I checked, you were dead.
大家都以为你死了
Everyone thought you were dead.
我以为你不在了
I've been trying to hold this city by myself
所以我独自努力守护这座城市
because I thought you were gone.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
还有劳蕾尔  我爸爸
To Laurel, to my dad...
-费利西蒂  -他们都不在了
- Felicity-- - They're gone.
-所有的人  -什么意思
- All of them. - What do you mean?
-奥利  -死了
- Ollie-- - Gone.
你要我怎么说  莎拉
What do you want me to say, Sara?
三十年前  你和雷跳上了飞船
30 years ago, you and Ray hopped on a spaceship,
-就再也没回来  -会回来的
- and you never came back. - We will.
我不想这么说
I don't want to say that...
如果当时你和雷没离开
things would have ended differently
事情的结果也许会不一样  但
if you and Ray had been here, but--
但如果我们没离开  事情可能会不一样
But if we were, it could've made the difference.
你都以为我死了  还来干什么
You thought I was dead. What are you doing here?
我们要找费利西蒂・斯莫克当年在研究的
We were looking for a Neuromorphic Prototype
神经形态原型
that Felicity Smoak was working on.
遭遇这一切后费利西蒂就离开了
Felicity left after everything that happened.
她公司所有的研究
Everything her company was working on
都被放在亚当斯和奥尼尔大街的一个仓库里
is being kept in a warehouse at Adams and O'Neil.
-入口密码是4587  -谢谢你
- Entry code is 4-5-8-7. - Thank you, Mr.--
你们从哪进来
You found your way in...
就从哪离开
find your way out.
我得承认你这建议不错  灰老头
I got to admit, that wasn't bad advice, Grey.
那你和桑德斯小姐的事还顺利吧
So things went well with Ms. Saunders?
当然
Oh, yeah.
我还有好消息要告诉你
Well, I have more good news.
我非常确定
I was able to very subtly confirm
雷蒙德对你的暗恋对象
that Raymond has no romantic inclinations
完全没有非分之想
towards your crush object.
等理清我的感情生活之后
Okay, well, once we've sorted out my love life,
得好好更新一下你的词汇量
we need to update your vocabulary.
迫不及待啊
Can't wait.
我去看看肯德拉
I'm gonna go check on Kendra.
-自信点  -明白
- Hey-- confidence. - Yeah.
我已经让原始阻尼器重新连上线了
I got the initial dampeners back online.
等其他队友带回
On the rest of the team returns
神经形态原型
with the Neuromorphic Prototype,
吉迪恩就能重新上岗了
Gideon will be good to go.
好极了
Excellent.
我们越早离开这里越好
Sooner we get out of here, the better.
-顺便谢谢你  -谢什么
- And thank you, by the way. - Whatever for?
在你和我提起之前
Well, till you mentioned it,
我没想到我对肯德拉还有这种想法
I hadn't really thought about Kendra in that way,
因为她和卡特
because, you know, she and Carter
这辈子是注定要在一起的
were destined to be together in this lifetime,
但是一切都变了
but it's all changed
她很特别
and, uh, you know, she's quirky
既幽默又漂亮
and funny and beautiful
而且焊接技术一流
and a pretty good welder.
那么
So-- you know,
你要把那些全抛诸脑后了吗
what about all those things we were talking about?
我们的任务等等
The mission and so forth?
我们都是成年人嘛
Oh, well, we're all adults here, right?
更深入些交往
Getting to know each other a little bit better,
也不会妨碍我们拯救世界
it's not gonna stop us from saving the world.
天呐
Oh, boy.
是谁邀请他们来的
Who invited them?
谣言说丧钟对某事很生气
Word on the street is Deathstroke is pissed about something.
丧钟是什么破名字
Deathstroke-- what kind of name's that?
派对结束了  大家都出去
Party's over. Everyone hit the streets.
告诉所有人
Hit everybody on them.
我要绿箭侠看不见明天的太阳
I want Green Arrow dead by morning.
这些都是我的人
Listen, pal, this is my gang.
他们只听命于我
The only orders they take are from me.
也许他们归你管  但这座城市归我管
Hmm, might be your gang, but it's my city.
绿箭侠的同伙是一个白衣女刺客和
Green Arrow is running with a female assassin in white
一个穿棕外套的英国佬
and a Brit in a brown coat.
把他们都干掉
Kill them all.
都听到指示了  行动吧
Heard the man. Let's go.
看来你的新喽
Looks like your new minions
要对里普和莎拉
are about to go on a citywide manhunt
-展开全市追捕  -那又怎么样
- for Rip and Sara. - So what?
他们要杀我们的朋友
They're gonna kill our friends.
他们怎么变成我们的朋友了
Since when did they become our friends?
这得问你
You tell me.
你和雷蒙德在俄国时关系似乎挺好的
You and Raymond seemed to get pretty tight back in Russia.
我从没和别人关系好过
I've never been tight with anyone.
米克  该走了
Mick, it's time to go.
-你又不是我老大  -我就是
- You're not the boss of me. - Actually, I am.
好吧  咱们都深呼吸冷静一下
Okay, let's both take a deep breath.
然后咱们来做笔交易
And we'll make ourselves a deal.
咱们一起去帮里普和莎拉
You help me get to Rip and Sara.
一旦他们安全了 咱们再谈这事
Once they're safe, we can have this conversation.
公平吗
Fair?
斯莫克科技
谢谢你愿意陪我们过来  狄格尔先生
Thank you for agreeing to accompany us, Mr. Diggle.
我叫康纳
It's Connor.
我不需要待在奥利弗・奎恩的身边
It's not like I needed to stick around Oliver Queen for anything.
-你事先知道吗  -知道什么
- Did you know? - Know what?
我的城市会变成这样
That this is what would happen in my city?
奥利弗说事情发展成这样的
Oliver said that the only reason
唯一原因就是
that things got so bad
我和雷当时没在这里帮忙
is because Ray and I weren't there to help.
应该是吧
I suspected that might be the case,
但其实这是件好事
but that's actually a good thing.
现在  一旦我们的任务完成
Now, once our mission is complete
你和帕尔默博士就能返回2016年的星城
and you and Dr. Palmer are returned to Star City in 2016,
你俩就可以阻止格兰特・威尔逊的大起义
you will both be present to stop Grant Wilson's Uprising.
这个未来只是一条可能的时间线
This future is only a potential timeline.
所以星城不一定会
So this-this version of Star City--
变成这个样子吗
this doesn't have to happen?
没错  未来一直在变化
Correct. The future is always in flux.
希望不会变成这样
Hopefully, this will never come to pass.
这个世界不是真实的
This world isn't real.
我们分开找  可以搜查更多地方
Let's split up. We'll cover more ground.
斯莫克科技
你好  宝贝
Hello, beautiful.
敌人为数众多
There's too many of them!
先生们  你们来得正是时候
Gentlemen, your timing is exemplary.
康纳在哪
Where's Connor?
他被抓走了
He's been taken.
他们是格兰特・威尔逊的人
These are Grant Wilson's men.
只有半张脸全身穿着装甲的人
The guy with the half face and the body armor
看来挺喜欢穿连帽衫的孩子的
has a real mad-on for the kid in the hoodie.
-跟我谈一下  -里普
- Can I have a word? - Rip--
我知道你想说什么
I know what you're going to say.
-我们要把他救回来  -就是这事
- We have to get him back. - Yes, that.
你忘了这个未来
You're forgetting this future
只是一条可能的时间线
is only a potential timeline.
格兰特・威尔逊就在这时杀死康纳
Yeah, where Grant Wilson kills Connor.
威尔逊不会杀死康纳的
Wilson's not going to murder Connor,
因为当你回到2016年
because once you're returned to 2016,
威尔逊或康纳都不存在
there won't be a Wilson or a Connor,
至少他们不是现在这个样子
at least not as we know them both right now.
既然他们得救了  那咱们接着谈
Now that we rescued them, let's have that chat.
你想留在这里
You want to stay here.
我以为我已经讲得很清楚了
Thought I made that pretty clear.
我不清楚的是  你为什么不想留下
What I'm less clear on is why you don't.
城里全是窃贼和罪犯
A city of thieves and criminals--
感觉会有很多竞争对手
Sounds like a lot of competition.
把他们全部干掉
Then we wipe them out.
我怎么干掉那个人
What I did to that other guy,
我们就怎么干掉格兰特・威尔逊
we do the same thing to this Grant Wilson
还有任何挡路的蠢猪
and anyone else stupid enough to get in our way.
看看四周吧  史纳特
Take a look around, Snart.
这就像梦一样
We're living the dream.
是啊  说到这里...
Yeah. Speaking of which...
睡个好觉  伙计
Sleep tight, buddy.
他怎么了
What happened to him?
意见不合
Difference of opinion.
好吧
Right.
我们要把这个和罗里先生带回乘波号
We need to get this and Mr. Rory back to the Waverider.
杰佛逊  来得正好
Oh, Jefferson, perfect timing.
我需要你的机械知识
I'm in need of your mechanical acumen.
好吧  咱们开始吧
Okay, let's do it.
怎么了  你干了什么
What? What did you do?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你干坏事了  你干了什么
You did something. What did you do?
没什么  没什么
Nothing, nothing.
你知道  这心灵感应
You know, this psychic connection thing,
可是双向的
it goes both ways
从我走进来
and the moment that I walked in here,
我就感到非常焦虑和内疚
I started feeling really anxious and guilty.
你感到内疚  你干了什么
You feel guilty, so what did you do?
听我解释  我都是为了你好
In my defense, I was only acting in your best interests.
你干了什么
What did you do?
可能在我试图弄清
It's possible in my attempt to discern
帕尔默博士是否想和你抢桑德斯小姐时
whether Dr. Palmer had competing feelings for Ms. Saunders--
你不是吧
Oh, you didn't--
我也许不小心激发了
I may have inadvertently prompted him
他对她其他方面的
to think of her in ways in which...
情感
he hadn't.
-灰老头  -对不起
- Ugh, Grey! - I'm sorry.
我的本意是很好的
My intentions were honorable.
算了  没关系
Ah, it's cool.
-没关系吗  -对
- Is it? - Yeah.
也没什么影响
I mean, nothing's really changed apart from the fact
只是现在我得和人竞争
that now I got competition I didn't have before,
但我还是要对自己有信心
but I should still have confidence in myself.
对吗
Right?
对
Right.
他们回来了
Oh, they're back.
罗里先生呢
Where's Mr. Rory?
睡着了
Sleeping it off.
我们拿到了神经形态原型
We have the Neuromorphic Prototype.
飞船引擎有进展吗
Any luck with the ship's engines?
有  已经修好了
Yeah, it's all good.
发生什么事了  兰斯小姐
Is there something wrong, Ms. Lance?
我的家人和朋友全都死了
Well, all my friends and family are dead,
只有奥利弗・奎恩活着  可他只是个躯壳了
except for Oliver Queen, who happens to be dead inside
还失去了左臂
and missing his left arm.
莎拉  我告诉过你
Sara, I have told you--
这个未来还没固定
That this is just a potential future
等我们回到2016年
and that it's all gonna go back
如果我们回得去的话
when we return to 2016--
一切都会变回原样
if we return.
但如果我们回不去了呢
But what if we don't?
我们都知道卡特回不去了
We all know Carter's not coming back.
我们从事的也不是最安全的工作
It's not like we have the safest line of work.
如果莎拉想留下帮忙  我们就应该留下
I think if Sara wants to stay and help that then we should.
当初我们加入这个团队就是为了当英雄
I mean, that's what we signed up for: to be heroes.
我赞成杰佛逊的想法
I agree with Jefferson.
是  你们当然都这么想
Yes, of course you both do,
因为你们都不知道改变时间线造成的隐患
because neither of you understand the pitfalls of changing the timeline.
干预未来无疑比改变过去更危险
Meddling with the future is arguably more dangerous
因为未来还没固定
than changing the past, because it is still in flux.
你的妻儿会在未来死去
Your wife and son's death are in the future.
-你就想让我们改变它  -别跟我来这套
- You want us to change that. - Don't play that card with me.
那又怎么样
So what?
你只愿意为了自己的家人拿时间线冒险吗
Are you only willing to risk the timeline if it's your own family?
我不只是为了救我的家人
I am not just trying to save my family
也不只是为了救一座城市
and I'm not just trying to save one city,
而是拯救整个世界
but the entire world!
自私的人不是我  莎拉
I'm not the one being selfish, Sara.
下地狱吧你
Go to hell.
也许会吧
Most likely.
如果你想去救霍克先生
If you want to go and save Mr. Hawke,
随你的便
then be my guest.
我会让飞船在这里停一小时
I'll keep the ship here for one hour,
然后就起飞
then we're leaving.
不管你有没有上船
With you on board or without.
你好啊  米克
Hello, Mick.
你这个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
冷静点
Just calm down.
你欺骗了我
You lied to me!
又不是第一次了
Wouldn't be the first time.
记得德雷货币兑换处吗
Remember the Delray Currency Exchange?
还有黑鹰装甲车那次
The Black Hawk Armored Car job?
如果我当时没欺骗你
If I hadn't lied to you on those scores,
我们都会进监狱  或者已经死了
we'd both be in prison or dead.
我是出主意的  你是出力气的
I'm the brains. You're the muscle.
一直都是这样
That's how it's always been.
而在某些时候  我必须临危制变
And on occasion, I've had to call some audibles.
你总喜欢自讨苦吃  米克
You have a habit of getting in your own way, Mick.
你说得对
You're right.
之前干一票的时候你欺骗我
You've lied to me about jobs before,
然后你又欺骗我我们这是在干一票
but then again, you lied to me about this being a job.
你现在在意的不是那些金银财宝了
It's not about the score anymore for you.
你宁愿拯救世界也不愿做我的搭档
You'd rather save the world than be my partner.
团队意识真强啊
A real team player.
因为要打败萨维奇就必须团结一致
'Cause that's what it's gonna take to defeat Savage.
然后呢  更有钱  更有权
Then what? More money? More power?
过舒适而罪恶的一生
A life of leisure and sin?
你不明白吗  米克
Don't you get it, Mick?
如果我们干掉萨维奇这个永生的恶魔
If we take out Savage, this immortal monster,
你没发现我们会有什么好处吗
can't you see what that gets us?
没有  你说说看
No, tell me.
我们就会成为史上最坏的大坏蛋
We'd be the two baddest sons of bitches of all time.
我不想被人列队欢迎
I don't want a ticker tape parade.
你知道我对这个世界的期许
You know what I want from this world.
知道
Yes...
你想看它烧起来
to see it burn.
你再对我动手
You lay a hand on me again,
我也会让你烧起来
you'll burn too.
奥利弗
Oliver.
Oliver!
不是叫你走了吗
Thought I told you to go.
康纳被格兰特・威尔逊抓走了
Grant Wilson has Connor.
他们会把他杀了
They're gonna kill him.
他知道自己在干什么
He knew what he was signing up for
你也知道我帮不了他
and you know there's nothing I can do to help him.
这不是我认识的奥利弗・奎恩
That's not the Oliver Queen that I know.
也许我已经不是从前的我了
Maybe I'm not that person anymore.
看看我  莎拉
Look at me, Sara.
我其实只是半个从前的我
I'm literally half the man I used to be.
这座城市需要那半个你
Then that's the half this city needs.
他手下有很多人  奥利
He's got too many men, Ollie.
我一个人应付不来
I can't do this by myself.
那你的朋友呢
What about your friends?
只有我一个人
I'm on my own--
除非有人帮我
unless I'm not.
别逼我  莎拉
Come on, Sara.
我没有机会问康纳
I never got the chance to ask Connor
他为什么要穿连帽衫  但我知道原因
why he wears the hood, but I know why.
因为这座城市
It's because this city
永远需要绿箭侠
will always need a Green Arrow.
飞船准备好启程了吗
Is the ship ready for departure?
没有  兰斯女士还没登船
No, Ms. Lance is not yet onboard.
我给了她一小时的时间
I gave her an hour.
时间太紧了
Hardly enough time for--
现在已经过去一小时半了
And she's been 90 minutes.
我们还要等多久
How much longer are we supposed to wait?
哪怕这个未来还没固定
It doesn't matter that this is a potential future.
哪怕这可能
It doesn't matter that this
根本不会发生
may never come to pass--
根本不会成真
may never be real.
但对莎拉来说  眼前的就是真的
For Sara, this is very real.
我知道  所以我多给了她半小时
I know, which is why I gave her an extra 30 minutes.
吉迪恩  飞船情况如何
Gideon, what's our status?
乘波号运作正常  船长
The Waverider is operational, Captain,
但我不能保证能维持多久
but I can't guarantee for how long.
-解释一下  -我们虽然隐身了
- Explain. - We are cloaked,
但和城里的犯罪分子聚集来见证
but positioned dangerously close to where the city's criminal element
康纳・霍克被处决的地点十分靠近
is gathering to witness the execution of Connor Hawke.
等得越久  暴露船体以及
The longer we wait, the greater the risk
飞船再次受创的风险就越大
of detection and further damage to the ship.
你真的愿意冒险
Do you really want to risk
永远被困在这样的2046年吗
being marooned in this version of 2046 forever?
我更不愿把莎拉留在这里
Certainly more than I want to maroon Sara here.
她是我们的朋友  我们的队友
She's our friend. Our teammate.
如果我们在阻止萨维奇的过程中
What's the point of stopping Savage
跟他一样冷血  又有什么意义呢
if we only become as immoral as he is in the process?
你应该感到光荣
You should be honored.
这里可是神圣之地
This is hallowed ground.
我正是在这里废了
I took Oliver Queen's arm
奥利弗・奎恩的手臂
in this very spot.
那就放开我
Well, then let me go,
看看我跟奎恩
and we'll see which one of us is tougher,
谁更厉害
me or Queen.
我已经知道答案了
I already know the answer to that.
把囚犯压好
Ready the prisoner.
老大
Sir.
我们发现她想从边上溜进来
We saw her trying to sneak past the perimeter.
太不小心了
Sloppy.
刺客联盟应该会感到羞愧
The League of Assassins would be embarrassed.
你有什么计划
What was your strategy here?
你真的以为你今晚可以溜进来
You really think you could just turn up tonight...
把我杀了吗
kill me?
不是
No.
我只是来分散你的注意力
It was just my job to distract you.
你不是绿箭侠
You're not Green Arrow.
你只是穿着万圣节化装服的废物
You're just a punk in a Halloween costume.
挺逗的  我正想对你说同样的话
Funny, I was gonna say the same thing about you.
你想和真的绿箭侠打吗
You want to fight the Green Arrow?
我就在这里
I'm right here.
你们是怎么说服里普留下的
How did you convince Rip to stay?
实际上  派援兵过来是他的主意
Actually, sending in the cavalry was his idea.
奎恩先生在哪
Where's Mr. Queen?
康纳
Connor!
全部都是胆小鬼
Cowards, all!
奥利弗
Oliver?
再见到你们真好  雷  肯德拉
It's good to see you again, Ray. Kendra.
多谢相助
Thanks for the assist.
那么他是谁
So who's that?
他叫格兰特・威尔逊
His name is Grant Wilson.
曾经  他的父亲  斯莱德
Once upon a time, his father, Slade,
想要毁掉我的生活
tried to ruin my life.
那可不是个和谐的家庭
That's not a nice family.
那一发射得真准  约翰
That's good shooting, John.
是康纳
It's Connor.
总之
Either way,
你是绿箭侠
it's Green Arrow.
我们有很多活干
We have a lot of work to do.
格兰特・威尔逊成功地
Grant Wilson did a good job
把城中的犯罪分子都聚集到一起
of keeping the criminal element in the city together.
他们很快又会组织起来
Now, there will be plenty of people to fill the vacuum.
我想留下来
I feel like I should stay.
雷离开前
Before Ray left,
告诉过我里普为什么要招募你们
he told me why Rip brought all of you together.
你的使命很重要  莎拉
It's important, Sara.
我不想让你一个人
I just hate the idea
收拾残局
of leaving you here to fix it alone.
我不是一个人
I'm not alone.
你要小心  知道吗
Just--just be careful, all right?
你应该最清楚
Well, you should know better than most
我很少会这么做
I rarely ever am.
照顾好他
You watch his back.
遵命
Copy that.
我们开工吧
Let's get to work.
我要自信点
All right, confidence.
Confidence. Okay.
我猜里普可能
So, uh, I think Rip might have
在他的柜子里藏了些伏特加
some of that vodka left in his cabinet.
然后呢
And?
然后
And...
我们喝一杯吧
maybe we could get a drink?
你是要约我吗
Are you asking me out?
是的  我想是吧
Yes? No. I think so.
可以吗
Is that okay?
当然没问题
Yeah, that-- that's totally okay,
只是三个月前
except that three months ago,
我是个再普通不过的人
I was a completely normal person
而现在我是鹰女神
and now I'm a hawk goddess
穿越时间
traveling through time,
努力不让自己被一个永生疯子杀害
trying to avoid being killed by an immortal psychopath
而他则杀了我的真命天子
who murdered the man I was destined to be with.
所以
So...
对不起  雷  我...
I'm sorry, Ray. I--
我想我的生活已经够复杂了
I think my life's complicated enough
我承受不了其他事了
without throwing whatever this is into the mix.
好  我完全明白
Yeah, totally understand.
如果我是古埃及女祭司转世
If I was a reincarnated Egyptian priestess,
我也会这样想
I'd probably feel the same way.
我去看看斯泰因教授
I'm gonna go check on Professor Stein.
没问题了
All good here.
-完全没问题了  -没事吧
- Absolutely no problems. - Everything okay here?
没事  没事  你呢
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, fine. You?
我很好  我很好
Oh, yeah, good. Good. It's good.
你听到了多少
How much of that did you hear?
听得挺全的  我很抱歉
Uh, enough. I'm sorry.
我也很抱歉
Sorry too.
所以你知道我...
Wait, you knew that I--
你藏不住你的心思
You're not that subtle.
顺便告诉你  她会选我的
She would've picked me, by the way.
你就继续做梦吧
Keep telling yourself that.
她会选我的
She would've.
我在研究我们的下一个目的地
I'm just working on determining our next destination.
你提议的地狱我考虑过了
I've considered your suggesting of hell,
我决定暂时先不去了
but I think I'll give it a miss for the time being.
我只是想谢谢你
I ju st wanted to say thank you
让队友们来支援我
for sending the team to back me up.
事实证明  你是对的
As it turns out, you were right.
这句话很难说出口吧
That must've been hard to say.
如今我不得不承认
Of late I've discovered
我还有很多要学的
that I still have a lot to learn, I admit.
我发现所有的未来都值得我们为之战斗
Including the fact that every future is worth fighting for.
所以...
That said...
这个任务还会继续
this mission is going to continue
我们还会面对很多艰难的抉择
to present us with difficult choices,
我想确定你还是不是我们的一员
and I need to know that you are a member of this team.
我想是吧
I guess so.
吉迪恩  让我们看看
All right, Gideon, let's see if these repairs
马丁  雷和杰克斯是不是完全修好了
that Martin, Ray, and Jax made are up to scratch.
在我看来  桑德斯小姐
As far as I can tell, Ms. Saunders
完成了大部分工作  而那两位男士
did most of the work, while the two gentlemen
-则在互相角逐...  -赶紧启程吧
- competed for-- - Just get us out of here.
赶紧了  吉迪恩
Please, Gideon.
我会想念这里的
I'm gonna miss this place.
他们挺像你这类人的
Yeah, they really seemed like your kind of people.
我已经不知道我是哪类人了
I don't know who my people are anymore.
下一站去哪里  船长
So where to next, Captain?
这个任务美在我们的下一站
Well, the beauty of this mission is that
不是哪里  而是哪一年
the real question is not where, but when.
因此  我们就在萨维奇防不胜防时
In which case, I suggest that we next hit
给他下一击吧
Savage when he least expects it.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv